Speaker 1: Remember that when
Speaker 2: you walk out of here. This next person has
become a
Speaker 2: really great friend of mine. His name is Rogan O'Hanley, and I'm so happy. There's so many people that are fighting just so many different fronts of the same war. You know, I do what I do, I'm on stage. You know, there are people that give money and donate to causes to make sure that we can have a voice. It takes so many people to win a war. There are people that are online making memes to take really complex...
Speaker 2: Issues and break it down. It's just a funny meme and Rogan O'Hanley is one of those people. How many people know DC Drano on Instagram?
Yeah, he actually has
Speaker 2: a real name. It's not DC Drano. It's it's Rogan O'Hanley, and I want to show you a video of what he does
Hey
Speaker 3: everyone, DC Drano here. So in my last video of me
Speaker 4: walking through Hollywood with my MAGA hat, I wanted to send a message that we the people are reclaiming our streets from leftist political thugs like Antifa. That video did pretty well, but I kept reading in the
Speaker 5: comments of "Oh, you only walked through Hollywood. Why don't you try walking through Compton and see
what
Speaker 6: happens?"
Speaker 6: Compton, it's a pretty bad rap. Most people wouldn't drive through here without a Bible, a prayer, and a bulletproof vest. Well,
let's
Speaker 7: do
Speaker 8: it. Today I'm going to be walking through Compton with my MAGA hat. I'm not bringing any weapons or any protective
Speaker 9: gear. It's just me, my camera, and a damn important message that I want to send to mainstream media, Hollywood celebrities, and these corrupt political leaders.
Thank
Speaker 10: you.
Speaker 10: What up, Dragon? What up?
I got
Speaker 10: something to say. Without
further ado, I'm
Speaker 11: sorry guys, he's not going to be here. He actually got shot in Compton. I'm kidding. Rogan
Speaker 12: O'Hanley, also known as DC Drano.
Oh, sometimes I get a
Speaker 13: good feeling
Thank you,
Speaker 13: everybody. Is that what my voice really sounds like? Yeesh, sorry. A lot
of you are
Speaker 14: probably thinking, why would you do that? You're crazy. And
you would have a
Speaker 14: lot in common with my mother. But
I said, Mom,
Speaker 15: listen, this is your fault. No.
She's
Speaker 15: like, "What?"
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): I said, "Growing up, watching you with three kids, by herself, no college degree,
working multiple
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): part-time jobs, waitressing, cleaning toilets, cleaning houses, she had no choice, you know? We
Speaker 14: even lived on welfare for a little bit. But watching
her
do what
Speaker 14: she did to raise her kids, you know? I learned
Speaker 17: that it's not about talking the talk when it's something you believe in or something you have to do. It's about walking the walk.
So that's
Speaker 17: what I did. I took a
walk. Not a walk I
Speaker 17: would recommend.
And some
Speaker 18: people ask, you know, why did you do it? Were you just trying to provoke people? Were you trying to troll the
libs?
kill
Speaker 18: yourself I don't know I said no it's none of that I wanted
Speaker 14: to do something
that would
Speaker 14: show just how much I believed in the message that I delivered at the end of that
video right
Speaker 14: so it's not
Speaker 18: about the walk it was about my speech at
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): the end
and I
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): found the safest spot I could in Compton it was like a parking lot
and I was
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): Strip mall. Turns out,
I was
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): wearing the MAGA hat. It was actually a blood territory.
So, got
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): lucky there.
But I gave a speech at the
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): end. I went to Compton City Hall, which was symbolic, but also right next to a police station.
And I talked
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): about
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): what I thought Trump was going to do to be the best
Speaker 19: president for black Americans
Speaker 20: in this country since Abraham Lincoln freed the slaves from Democrats
back in the 1800s. I said his
Speaker 21: economic policies are going to juice up the economy
That he's
Speaker 14: going to renegotiate these trade deals, and it's going to bring middle-class jobs back from overseas into America. That
he's
Speaker 15: going to reform our prison systems. And
that he's going to
Speaker 15: do more to unify this country along racial lines than Obama ever could. And you know what? It's only
Speaker 22: been two years, and I've already been proven right.
He signed an executive
Speaker 23: order.
Speaker 14: That's allocating billions of dollars in investments into low-income communities, okay? We have almost record-low food stamps, but record-high wages. Record-low unemployment for black and
Speaker 20: Hispanic people, and record-high optimism. The American
Speaker 24: dream is being restored right
now.
and we
Speaker 24: all benefit.
So, the
Speaker 15: secretary of the Housing and Urban Development Administration, guy named Dr. Ben Carson.
About a week ago, I
Speaker 25: think, he said he's gonna put
Speaker 14: out a policy
Speaker 14: that is going to say illegal immigrants can no longer live in federal public housing.
They think it's
Speaker 15: over 75,000 homes across this country that illegal immigrants are living in
Speaker 15: When we have
Speaker 24: record homelessness in Los Angeles and San Francisco, those units are going to be opened up to Americans, to black and Hispanic Americans that deserve them, that paid into the system, and that are rightfully owed that benefit.
And I remember when I
Speaker 26: lived in Los Angeles, who here remembers on Hollywood's, Trump's star on Hollywood Boulevard, right?
Speaker 26: Lots of battles there. There was a moment
Speaker 27: where there was this homeless woman, a black homeless woman.
Do you guys
Speaker 27: remember this? She held up a
sign.
Speaker 28: And this group of leftist thugs started beating her up.
They were
Speaker 28: kicking her while she was down. They threw her cart.
Speaker 21: They ripped up her sign.
They were
Speaker 21: yelling at her while she was down, saying, you got what you deserve. You spewed hate and you got hate. You know what her sign said? 20 million illegals in this country and
Speaker 20: homeless Americans are sleeping on the street. And
now that's
Speaker 20: being changed.
Speaker 29: Thank you to Dr. Ben Carson.
And
Speaker 23: honestly, I hope she's out there smiling a little bit. I hope she heard that story and I hope she
Speaker 20: gets some help. But these are historic changes that Obama failed to make. In my opinion, I think
he did it
Speaker 20: intentionally. The illusion of helping, but keeping
Speaker 27: them dependent on government and then rinsing and repeating the cycle every year. "Oh, we're going to be the ones that help
you."
"Those
Speaker 18: racist guys though,
oh no, no." But
Speaker 18: it's all a lie, it's all a lie. So for
those
Speaker 23: that don't know me, I am a lawyer.
I lived in Hollywood. I went
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): to Northeastern University in Boston. Pretty liberal.
Somehow got
Speaker 15: elected president of student government
there.
They knew I
Speaker 15: was conservative, too. Newspaper did not like me. I
went to
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): law school
at
Speaker 30: University of Chicago. I
lived on the south
Speaker 30: side of Chicago. I had
the same
Speaker 30: barber as Obama. I'm not even kidding. Pretty
good haircut, I've
Speaker 30: got to say. But
I lived on the
Speaker 30: south side
of
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): Chicago. And I could have moved up north and hung out with a lot of my friends. But for some reason, I just wanted to stay there.
I was
Speaker 31: two blocks from his house. I was four blocks from Louis Farrakhan's house.
Kind of a crazy
Speaker 30: situation. South Side of Chicago is very interesting. A lot of beautiful culture, but a lot of corruption, a lot of communism.
And I
Speaker 30: remember
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): living in Chicago, the good part, that the West Side was basically a war zone. We all know this, right?
And
Speaker 27: then you would see these parents
on TV.
just
Speaker 27: grief-struck, sobbing,
Speaker 33: begging for help. Their kid just got killed, playing in the park. Drive by, stray bullet, took
him out.
Speaker 27: And they're crying, and they're begging for help. And then Democrats have the nerve to say, we're gonna be the ones that help you, and nothing gets done.
I couldn't believe
Speaker 34: it, and that's like what woke me up. I was like, these people are getting screwed over.
So I was
Speaker 15: practicing law in
LA,
I
Speaker 15: was doing deals with Matt Damon, Ben Affleck, Harvey
Speaker 35: Weinstein,
don't
Speaker 36: worry, don't worry. But these
Speaker 37: people, they would get up at their political
rallies, sorry, award shows, and
Speaker 14: They would point the finger, people like you, people like me, people like my parents, who did nothing but work their butts off, pay their taxes, take care
of their
Speaker 38: families, and they would say, you white people, you conservative people.
Speaker 27: You're the real problem in America. You're engaging in a war on women.
And then they
Speaker 27: would praise Harvey Weinstein. You're destroying this
Speaker 14: planet.
And then
Speaker 14: they go fly home in their private jet.
You want a
Speaker 14: racist wall?
And they go
Speaker 14: back to their mansion, surrounded by a wall.
Give up your guns. But let me keep
Speaker 20: mine in my armed security.
Amen.
So I
Speaker 20: couldn't take it anymore.
I couldn't
Speaker 30: take it anymore. And I started posting on Instagram a couple years ago. And I've got,
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): in a little over two years, over 500,000 followers just telling the truth.
Because
Speaker 15: fake news, Hollywood, they're all lying to us.
And it's
Speaker 15: something I want to hopefully inspire other people to
do.
Speaker 15: If some random white guy that drives a truck and
has a beard can
Speaker 19: post memes and then ultimately be speaking on a stage for Blexit...
Anything is
Speaker 39: possible. What's
interesting
Speaker 26: is
Speaker 18: that
Even
Speaker 18: though they point the finger at people like me, the white guy that lives in the south.
Okay, it's Florida. But
Speaker 40 (lower-pitched voice): to the
north, that is
Speaker 40 (lower-pitched voice): definitely
Speaker 41: the south.
Not to
Speaker 41: Texas. I
just couldn't take it anymore. And so I
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): decided to move to Florida. I visited for a weekend. And...
I
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): put in my notice at my job.
Speaker 42 (lower-pitched voice): I had a pretty cushy job. I was working really hard, getting way too much tax dollars taken out,
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): about, I think I took home like 62% of my money so I could pay $4.50 a gallon of gas to drive on roads that broke my suspension, and then to go home and watch politicians say, "You're the bad guy. We're gonna help the illegal
Speaker 40 (lower-pitched voice): immigrants."
Speaker 40 (lower-pitched voice): And we hate you, but please, continue to give us your tax dollars.
Two
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): days after Hillary got elected, an email went around my firm. We're going to be holding a support
group for
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): people that are upset about the election. Adult lawyers needed Play-Doh and
kittens. I
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): guarantee they would not have done the same thing if Trump had lost,
Speaker 44: for Trump supporters.
and so I felt
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): like I was living a double life I was posting these memes and then listening to these people in the hallway
Speaker 19: just say the worst things possible about Trump
and so I
Speaker 19: said that's it I'm out of here the money isn't
worth
Speaker 30: it on the way out
a competitor
Speaker 30: law firm heard that I was leaving they didn't know why I never told anyone
Speaker 42 (lower-pitched voice): I would get fired on the spot
and they
Speaker 42 (lower-pitched voice): said you know can I just meet you for lunch Rogan I
Speaker 40 (lower-pitched voice): was like okay
sure and
and
Speaker 40 (lower-pitched voice): she said what's it gonna take to hire you what would it take for you to come work for
me I
Speaker 42 (lower-pitched voice): said well the market rate is honestly like $400,000 that's how senior I was
but I think I'm
Speaker 42 (lower-pitched voice): moving to Florida and she says how about this $500,000 and
I make you partner
She could have said
Speaker 45: a million,
but I wasn't
Speaker 45: gonna take it. This moment in
Speaker 46: our country's history is too pivotal to sit back and watch America go off a cliff.
This is my public
Speaker 46: service. I said, we got four years to get this right, to protect this president,
and
Speaker 46: to save black America from 50 years of
Speaker 21: tragedy. This is our opportunity. This is what Blexit is all
about. The
Speaker 21: time is now, it's right now.
You can't
Speaker 21: put this off. You've taken the first step, you're here. And I thank all of you and I respect you for that. I want you to take the next step after this. I want you to stand strong and support this president.
and
Speaker 21: support this movement, support his policies, support his successes. 'Cause this is our one chance to get this right. They aren't gonna let Trump get by again.
So we need
Speaker 21: to stand strong and get this done.
I wanna tell you a quick
Speaker 14: story before I finish.
I've been doing
Speaker 14: some college
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): speaking. I've talked at Kansas State, Colorado University, Arizona State, all within the last three days, to be honest, it feels like.
I was
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): speaking at Towson University, which is right outside Baltimore. Baltimore has had some really tough times.
And
Speaker 14: the speech got interrupted by Black Lives Matter. There's about 15,
20 people. And
Speaker 14: they start chanting, and they said, why are you anti-black? And I'm like, of all people to call it anti-black, it's probably not the best
choice.
But I wanted to
Speaker 14: talk with them a little bit. They came in with rage,
but I
Speaker 14: came in with love
and dialogue. And I
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): talked with them, and you know, we talked about some police brutality issues, and I said, "I'm just
Speaker 42 (lower-pitched voice): curious, how many people here think the Democrat Party has actually helped black Americans over the last 40 years?"
Not a single
Speaker 47: one of them raised their
hand.
was
Speaker 47: shocked and
I said so
Speaker 47: why are you
Speaker 48: so mad
at me why are you
Speaker 34: defending them and
I could see
Speaker 34: their brains that's like turn over they're like wait what am I doing
but what that
Speaker 34: showed me is that
Speaker 26: we have an
opportunity we have
Speaker 26: Candace Owens leading this charge and we
Speaker 24: have these
people
open
Speaker 24: to this solution. They are open to it, I promise you. If Black Lives Matter in Baltimore
doesn't
Speaker 20: support the Democrat Party, then nobody really does when it comes
down to it.
Speaker 19: So we've got this one chance.
This is our
Speaker 19: revolution. This is a revolution. It's a peaceful revolution.
It's a
Speaker 26: revolution that
I
Speaker 26: don't think we've really seen since the 60s, 70s. And
I didn't
Speaker 26: think that I was going to say this tonight.
Speaker 49: I kind of went back and forth with it. I
think Candace
Speaker 49: Owens is our Martin Luther King.
Thank you.
once in
Speaker 50: a generation we're so lucky to have her
so just know that y'all
Speaker 43: are a part of history right now this is going to change the country they're going to write about this in history books so
let's get
Speaker 43: excited let's support president trump let's
Speaker 19: support blexit let's support candace and let's stop talking the talk like the democrats and let's start walking the walk thank you